<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
    <link>http://islamisangh.org/</link>
    <description>Islami Sangh, Nepal (previously known as Islami Yuwa Sangh, Nepal) was founded 28 years ago with the purpose of striving to establish Islam in its totality, in all aspects of human life as well as collective; from the reform of inner self to the external world. Islam provides to all section of society, the best means of equity and justice, wefare and reform, progress and prosperity, irrespective of race, region, or language.</description>
    <item>
       <title>History - Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
       <link>http://islamisangh.org/view/history</link>
       <description>Islami Sangh, Nepal (previously known as Islami Yuwa Sangh, Nepal) was founded 28 years ago with the purpose of striving to establish Islam in its totality, in all aspects of human life as well as collective; from the reform of inner self to the external world. Islam provides to all section of society, the best means of equity and justice, wefare and reform, progress and prosperity, irrespective of race, region, or language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
       <title>Ideology - Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
       <link>http://islamisangh.org/view/history</link>
       <description>The ISN, for attainment of its objective, is bounded principally by the Quran and the Sunnah. In the light of these sources, the organization adopts ethical, constructive, peaceful, democratic and constitutional means. It refrains from such activities, which are opposed to truth and honesty, or which are likely to provoke communal hatred, class conflict or social disorder. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
       <title>Mission - Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
       <link>http://islamisangh.org/view/mission</link>
       <description>1. Invitation to all human beings to turn to their Creator Allah (s.w.t.) and accept His Guidance. 2. Restoration of the character of muslim community in the light of Holy Quran and Sunnah. And awakening its sense of mission.3. Restoration of Human dignity, on the basis of unity of God and unity of Bani-Adam. 4. To avoid all kinds of sectarian prejudices and act according to the wishes of Allah (s.w.t).
       </description>
    </item>
    <item>
       <title>Organizational Expansion - Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
       <link>http://islamisangh.org/view/structure</link>
       <description>Alhamdulillah! ISN in it's mission has been working in 8 zones out of 14 zones in Nepal. Viz. Mechi, Koshi, Sagarmatha, Narayani, Bagmati, Gandaki, Lumbini and Bheri. Can be viewed in the Map below;
       </description>
    </item>
    <item>
       <title>Tarbiyah work cell - Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
       <link>http://islamisangh.org/view/tarbiyah-work-cell</link>
       <description>The ISN makes comprehensive attempt for all round intellectual, practical, moral and religious development of its adherents and for the refinement of their capabilities. It strives to strengthen their bond with Allah and inculcate in them a concern for the Hereafter and sense of devotion and obedience to the prophet (peace be upon him); so that they might become sincere followers of Islam, devoted workers for establishment of Deen and embodiments of sacrifice and perseverance in the true path.
       </description>
    </item>
    <item>
       <title>HUDA - Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
       <link>http://islamisangh.org/view/huda</link>
       <description>HuDA is a community based training center which has been established in Bagbazar, Kathmandu in 2009. HUDA is focusing on providing vocational training to the Muslims especially those who are from the low income sector
       </description>
    </item>
    <item>
       <title>Print Media - Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
       <link>http://islamisangh.org/media/Print</link>
       <description>Print media of Islami sangh Nepal
       </description>
    </item>
    <item>
       <title>Publication Media - Islami Sangh Nepal</title>
       <link>http://islamisangh.org/media/Publication</link>
       <description>Publication media of Islami sangh Nepal
       </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>